Don't push me away
Episode 10
Don't tell me to go away
Don't say that I bring misfortune.
Don't say I'm an animal
At least don't do this to me
You... are my man
I'm not your man, your highness
You are my man
You belong to me. You are mine!
You can't leave me without my permission
And you can't die either
Totally my man
Project coordinator, editor and translator of songs: Nemie
Translators: Nemie, Kaia, tamaramin
Sister?
Beta Editor: Sana
It can't be
You're wrong
Typesetters: Nemie, Sana
How is it that you left the palace?
How?
I'm sure. How could I not recognize her?
I even asked the security guard
How can a court lady leave the palace?!
Does So care about such things?
Probably took him by force
If they are caught, Su's life will be in danger
Let's find her
Give me a horse, and then...
- Stay here
- What?
It's not good for you to drive around at night
Go, I'll find them
Thanks for your concern, but I won't leave
It is already known that she left the palace
I don't even know what will happen to her
Let's find them together
Okay
I still think of you as a child
I'm sorry
I trust you
Will you hear him?
The same voice that is in such a hurry to confess
Are you still listening?
Can you hear my heart?
Neither you nor I will be safe
How raindrops settled on the window
Then maybe we can just run away?
If you want, we'll do it
Also my mind is consumed by you
Need you
I miss you
Even if I had to leave Songak, I wanted to bring you here
Will you hear him?
The same voice that is in such a hurry to confess
Are you still listening?
Can you hear my heart?
How raindrops settled on the window
Also my mind is consumed by you
Need you
I miss you
I'm always forced to leave
I still don't know why this is so
I've never brought misfortune
And I didn’t kill animals for pleasure
And people thoughtlessly too
Should I leave anyway?
It was just an illusion
Simple illusion
I shouldn't be afraid of him
He can't be allowed to become reckless.
I want you to live with a calm heart, Your Highness
Palace or other place
don't live in sorrow, don't shed blood, live in joy
I will... if you come with me
I'm a court lady
Should live in a palace
Then I won't leave
Besides, I...
I like another person
Beck Huh?
No, not Baek A
Then it's ok since it's not Baek Ah
If it's another man, then I can kill him
What?
The day Yong Hwa gave you a spanking,
from that day on I considered you my man
You saw what I was like
There was no need to explain or justify
Are you saying you're afraid? I don't believe
Only you are on my side
That's why I don't apologize
Not for the kiss, not for bringing me here
And one more thing
If I threaten and force someone to stop loving him,
I won't apologize
Accept
I wanted to give you something like this
I was just trying to help you
and never asked for your love
Then try to run away from me
You can throw it away if you want
Sister!
Su!
Where are you from?
Are they looking for me in the palace?
Fortunately, only Uk and I know
But others will soon discover
Let's go back
Here we go...
What are you doing?
I took her away, so I’ll bring her back too
If someone sees you two together,
rumors will start
This is a problem
Su
The Emperor has already given it to me
I am responsible for her
Gave it to you?
I will go with the 4th prince
Don't worry, come back
He said he'll take responsibility, so go ahead
Will you go with him?
Yes
Better stick to your words
Don't let Su get hurt
I don't want that either
Brother you can't let them go
There is no guarantee that Seo will head to the palace
I won't let her leave with him if he does that.
What?
This is the last time I let her go like this
Concubine... I just...
I was the one who took Su away unexpectedly, don't blame her
Are you saying she left the palace?
The Emperor gave me responsibility and asked for help
I should have left
However, she is a court lady,
and this may be considered a violation of the rules
So, are you going to punish her?
- Is it necessary?
- You must return, Your Highness
You don't need to be here to explain less to others about what happened.
I trust you, concubine O
Your little piece of kindness has taken up too much space in the 4th prince's heart
That's why I said that you don't fit in this place.
In the palace you can't just show your kindness to anyone
You need to watch your every step, as if you are walking on thin ice.
This is how you should live
I...
what should I do now?
We'll have to wait for the 4th prince's feelings to cool down
Bullseye!
You missed the target. Now I've seen everything
I need more days like this for me to improve my shooting skills
I always imagine someone before I kiss
The one who became a hero instead of me
If I imagine how this arrow pierces the heart
the one who kicked me out of my place
I won't miss
Bullseye!
What about you?
Who is your target?
I never
I don't think about anyone when I kiss
People without a clear goal are easy to manage
I'm leaving Songak
The Emperor sent me to die, but I have to return alive
You will be safe and sound
Of course. I'll be back in perfect condition
And think about it in my absence
Who can be an interesting target?
Do we have
Isn't there something we both agree on?
I'll be back soon
Until then you must think carefully
I'll be waiting for your return
Let's go
Are you angry?
The 4th prince and I just went to watch the sunrise
I didn't want to get you in trouble, so I came back with him.
I'm not angry
I'm just upset
I was always worried about leaving you in Damiwon
And So just took you away
I will ask the emperor to marry you
Marry?
When I heard that you were missing,
I remembered that you came here to marry the emperor
You don't know how worried I was that I might lose you again
I don't want to repeat the mistake again
Just like my wife said,
I could never sleep peacefully
Too much is expected of me, the future worries me
Even sleep is considered a crime by me.
You brought back laughter and joy to such a person
And... she gave me a poem
It was you
I want to leave the palace and live happily with you in Hwangju
I want to live, giving you the love that I didn’t give to my wife
Su,
will you become my wife?
He won't change
Won't hurt me
I'll be happy with him
If Gwangjong kills him...
Don't you want to be with me anymore?
No, that's not true!
So you don't believe my promise?
Everything is wrong...
Then will you answer me?
Will you marry me?
What's going on here?
The girl who spied on the princes while swimming... it's you!
Sorry, concubine O
Concubine Oh, I'll explain
If this secret meeting becomes known,
Who do you think will be executed first?
This place will be closed soon
Relationships with a court lady entail
loss of status and severe punishment
Let's go
I want you to leave the palace with me
What?
The doctor recommended that I leave the palace,
to restore strength and health
Come to my hometown with me, okay?
I was afraid that you were in a relationship with Prince Wang Wook
The best thing to do now is to avoid him.
8th Prince
asked me to marry him, and I thought about a positive answer
Think about the 4th prince!
Do you think you can survive between the two of them?
If either of them's feelings change, your life will be in danger.
8th Prince is different
- His feelings will remain the same
- No!
A palace is a place that makes people
take back your words and promises
That unknown general to whom I gave my heart...
Yes
As you might have guessed, he sits on the throne
He wanted to marry me, but he had to protect the throne
So he forgot about the small town herbal dealer's daughter
But I still wanted to be near him
And I made a promise to live like a court lady, not like a woman
I make tea and wash his hair
I prepare his clothes and dress him
I call my lover "Your Majesty"
I wash the bodies of the women he owns
Su, take a step back and look around
You could be in danger if you don't leave this place now.
The 8th Prince asked me to leave the palace and go to Hwangju
While he has no desire to seize the throne,
we can be happy
I trust him
I came to see if you're okay
I'll talk to concubine O
You need to rest today
Your Highness
Sign in
I will help you
I don't hate you or fear you, prince
Don't worry
Usually people
cling very tightly to a person,
who helped them in difficult times
They think that only this person is on their side
This man...
they call him a friend
Both love and friendship are a kind of sympathy, but...
They are different. Completely different
I'm afraid you're a little confused about these sympathies
That's why I'm worried
I'm actually worried
Maybe I couldn’t say then
I don't understand the difference between these feelings
Friendship or love
I kept everything a secret, I'm like this
for me it's the same thing
One feeling
How did it all start and when did it begin?
It's so hard to remember, but now I'm with you
It seems like you're trying to push me away
Do you think the same as me, I wonder?
These methods don't work for me.
This is the only thing that worries me now
This all looks so much like love, since I didn’t know
I told you to get ready
Now throw away your worries and hug
If the heart is beating, it's love, yes
Don't worry
Then just admit it to me
I won't do this again without your permission.
Sister Su!
Cham cham cham!
Oh, that's better
It would be stupid of me not to improve my skills after such a beating.
Cham cham cham!
Yes!
Here, you can hit with all your might
I'll be taken away if they see a lady of the court hitting a prince
By the way, I was so scared when I saw that you were taken by my 4th brother
Weren't you hurt?
Where did he take you?
We just went for a ride to get some fresh air
It was a lot of fun
He always does things his way
I don't like it
Try to understand your brother a little
You grew up in great love, prince
But he didn't receive it
He didn't have a real family
It's not easy to get kindness from people
It is also deserved by efforts
Since Seo returned to Songak, both Mom and Yeo have changed a lot.
You don't blame the 4th prince for this, do you?
I know it's not all his fault
If it weren't for him,
I would not have known about the worries that my mother and brother Yo were causing
Sister, I really miss the past
You know, when we spent time together
You were most beautiful when you smiled while living in Uka's house
I think about this often too
I want to go back
What did you just say?
On the holiday of the 9th day of the 9th lunar month
I will get the emperor's permission to marry Hae Soo
If she agrees to leave the palace, I will live with her in Hwangju
I know my family has big plans for me, but I don't need the throne.
Palace politics disgusts me
I just want to live in peace
Do you want to give up the throne?
Do you want to not care about mom and me and just live like an ordinary person?
What about us?
Who will protect Hwangbo's house?!
There are many ways to protect our home. I don't have to become emperor
Trust me
Have I ever stopped you from doing as you please?
If you are sure of what you want, then go ahead.
Make her yours
However, it won't be easy.
You must be well prepared
Su will be very grateful to you, mom
He needed to be stopped. You should have stopped him, Mom!
Even I'm tired of the battles for the throne
How do you think he feels?
There is a very heavy load on him, you can’t even imagine what it is.
Let's let him do as he pleases.
You were exiled for causing a miscarriage
from the concubine whom the emperor loved
This was just 10 years ago
Everyone knows that Empress Yu did it, but no one took our side
Concubine Kang, Concubine Park
Concubine Hong, Concubine Wang!
If we don't take the throne, they will attack again!
Crown Prince Mu is different from the Emperor
And the country will become different
Don't let unreasonable fears and worries get the better of you
I think it's time to step out from under your wing, Mom.
Yong Hwa
From now on I have a new goal
I will no longer be the emperor's daughter or sister
I will be like a deity who has power over the emperor
There's no need to forgive me
Empress, Princess Yeon Hwa has come to see you.
Princess Yeon Hwa?
You told me to visit you and tell you funny stories
I want to tell you one thing today
Really?
If you insist, I guess I should listen to her.
I'm looking forward to it
I heard there's a new girl
If I don't recognize her, then she's not a dancer
Let's see
Where...
Who... is here?
Have you been well, Zhong Ziqi?
Why are you here?
Who hired you to follow me?
Who are you?
I just came to play for the dancers
- Why follow you?
- Is it true?
It's you who always follows me, Zhong Ziqi
Don't remember?
I didn't know you were playing here
There are a lot of things I can't do.
But there is also a lot that I can do
I didn't know you were a gisaeng
Because of the way you communicated, I thought you were a noblewoman
Court musician or artist, just focus on work
Judging other people is a bad habit
We've already met three times, it's time to introduce ourselves
What's your name? Zhong Ziqi?
- Bok Soon
- Wu Hee!
It's time to go back to the rooms
Okay!
Bok Soon...
She's cheeky, of course.
Wu Hee. Woo Hee, as they said
And what will we do?
to make the Emperor and Crown Prince turn away from So?
We must convince the emperor
that the 4th prince is a rival to the crown prince
Pretend you support the 4th prince
Minister Park Young Gyu
Then I'll do the rest, empress
I handed over the papers regarding the Crown Prince's uncle to the 4th Prince
When these papers are revealed, the Crown Prince will suspect the 4th
Yeo is currently in Seogyeong meeting with Wang Sik Ryeom
Everything is perfect
We need to hurry up. Fine
Why would the Crown Prince visit his mother's family?
There are some issues he needs to sort out.
There's no need to bring this up
Yes, but brother
Is it true that you took Su away from the palace?
She's a court lady
If you treat her like an ordinary girl, both you and she will end up in trouble.
Don't make life difficult for her
I wasn't trying to get her into trouble
And it wasn’t my intention to complicate her life
I just made a mistake
I don't know how to build relationships with people
Can I be criticized for this?
I didn't know you cared so much about Su
In this world I only have you and her
Your Highness! Your Highness!
Jeongdeokjeong Palace is in uprising
The family of the crown prince's mother stole money from the people twice
Many powerful families want you to remove Crown Prince Mu
Crown Prince Mu, did you know about the embezzlement?
We have information that you were there when they came to collect their share of the money.
I found out about everything later
Maybe they miscalculated their part
You shouldn't talk like that
No one planned to steal from the residents who work so hard
Don't try to make false accusations
His Highness found out about this later
And is it also not true that your family is mired in bribery?
Emperor
We no longer want to entrust the future of our country to
immoral crown prince
- Please consider our request
If so,
Who would you like to see in Prince Mu's place?
Your... Your Majesty?
Are you saying that you will overthrow the crown prince?
To overthrow the prince, I need another candidate to take his place.
So I tell you to recommend another prince,
who can best rule Goryeo
Emperor, I believe the 4th Prince is the best fit
4th prince? Wang So?
Prince Wang So was adopted
He will have no maternal relatives who can tarnish his reputation
He also performed the rain ritual
After this, he earned the honor and respect of the imperial family and the entire people
I think he is more suitable for the role of the ruler of Goryeo than others
Sorry brother
I didn't think it would turn out this way
What are you talking about?
I was just worried about you, so I told So
I thought he cared about you the most
Just showed him your uncle's notes
Are you saying that 4th brother knew about my mother's family?
I... told him myself
I'm sure he knew
But I didn't know it would put your position in danger
Kill me brother
It's time to return to Shinzhu
You must leave after the 9th day of the 9th lunar month
Should I?
There are those who want to make you crown prince
Among them is your mother, Empress Yu
She's probably using you to gain the throne
I don’t communicate with them, why should I leave?
It's not fair
The heart of man can be tricky
It may not be true now, but if you continue to feel offended,
you will forget all the sincerity that is in you now
You were a shield from any arrows or failures,
what could have been waiting for him on the way
You have no idea that your father manipulated you
For you, Your Majesty,
my true feelings don't matter
I also want you to be with me as long as possible
But what can I do?
You need to cut the shoots before they grow
This is the whole palace
This should be served by that girl
Yes, concubine
I did everything as ordered
The Empress must not know anything about this matter.
Yes, prince...
I understood
Are you tired of bothering me yet?
When will you leave me alone?!
Didn't you want to become an emperor?
Mother must help her son's wishes come true
Don't worry
The throne will be yours if everything goes according to plan
Enough of these lies you feed me
I don't know what you're planning, but it won't work.
The Crown Prince will die on the 9th day of the 9th lunar month
I've already sent poison for him
Will enjoy the tea, you won't be able to stop him
Do you think that after learning this, I won’t do anything?
When they ask how you found out about the poison, what do you say?
From your mother?
If it's necessary, I'll tell you
Yes?
And I will say that I did this so that you could take the throne
To make you emperor
our whole family became so corrupt that they decided to poison the crown prince
We have already decided that we will ask the emperor for you
This is the whole palace
Everything will work only if we gnaw each other's tails
Try to stop it if you can
You will feel a noose around your neck that binds you
Nothing will happen according to you
The Emperor kicked you out, you still don’t realize it?
The maid who brings the tea will die and there will be no crown prince.
And you will take over everything
How... can I trust you?
You said so yourself
Even if you take the throne, you will not kill your brothers
I trust you
That's why I support
Why did the crown prince's star fade?
I asked you to wait
Why did you insist so much on the meeting?
Ask quickly
For the great escape we need to change ship
This is Goryeo, we are in the imperial palace
It's not that simple
Forget about intrigue
If you don't help kill the emperor,
all the people of Hupakje will know about your affairs
Will you be able to survive then?
As a child, when you called me "uncle", you were cute
Even if I don't help,
what can you do?
I knew you wouldn't agree so easily
How can you treat a court gisaeng like that?!
Please maintain your dignity!
I'll keep it a secret!
This is the court musician
Oh you little one..!
I thought you were cute
Get out!
This man...
Hey! Are you okay?
If you want to pretend you didn't see anything, do so
Be a virtue
So you don't need my help
With your skills you can have a great time here
This is yours, isn't it?
Apparently she wasn't going to look
Whatever you become if we meet again,
I won't forget to repay you, wife
I will keep my promise to you
I will love Hae Soo
Look after us please
Drink with your hands intertwined
This is what happened
Well let's
Who will you choose?
His Majesty has not yet been chosen
I wonder if he can avoid this fate again
Okay, I'll choose...
Jeong. I want to drink this cup with you
I don't want to! I'm a man, why should I do this?
Refusal is a bad omen!
Come on
Then should we start?
First, if the round flower rises high,
then the poles of the world too
Second
Having no other flowers,
pure yellow earth
Third
What goes around comes around
such is the virtue of man
Fourth
A flower that can fight frost
will grow strong and even
Fifth
Fifth... Fifth...
Fifth...
- Five...
- Fifth!
If there are flowers in your drinks,
the food will be fresh
This is what Zhong Hui said about chrysanthemum flowers
Well done, Vaughn
Jeong, martial arts is good,
but don't forget about studying
Yes, Your Majesty
What's the matter?
The Crown Prince seems to
you have no appetite today
Drinking is bad today.
I apologize for the confusion this has caused.
Why don't we drink chrysanthemum tea?
It is known for its health benefits
Concubine Oh, go and bring the prince his chrysanthemum tea
Yes, I listen to you
The Crown Prince wished for chrysanthemum tea
Wait a minute
Su, could you carry the tea for me?
I think I'm about to come down with a cold
I'm sorry
Concubine O told me to stay away and not serve the princes
So there's nothing you can do
Are you okay?
Faster!
We are late because you took a long time to prepare, now the emperor will be upset
What kind of expression is this?
You don't think we're late
because I overslept?
You should be ashamed
Greetings, Your Highness
I told you to hurry
You must accept her greeting
- What?
- If you don't do this...
she will have to continue standing in this position
Raise your head
I don't want to see you. Quickly turn away
Yes
From now on, always turn away
whenever we see each other
Do you understand?
I'm in a bad mood so I'm going back
You can stay or come with me
If this hurts you so much, why didn't you become his second wife?
Your love is enough to
accept him that way
Please keep an eye on him
Try to keep him out of the way
into senseless fights in the palace
He's easy to get hooked on, so don't let him get close to anyone.
Now I'm his wife! You don't have to worry about it anymore!
We'll check the tea first
Crown Prince, I need
tell you something
Then speak
In fact...
The maid who brings the tea will die
- and there will be no crown prince
- I brought chrysanthemum tea
Thank you
So, were you talking about something?
Yes
I've been giving you trouble lately
Like your brother I would like
receive three drinks from you,
to strengthen our relationship
Well said
But this is tea, not booze.
What should we do?
I think with my mood today I'll get drunk even from tea
Give it to the 4th prince
Yes, your highness
I've done a terrible thing
It's my fault
Before this I touched chrysanthemum flowers and there was oil left on my hands
Give me a new cup
I'll drink the first one to your longevity
Second for continuing your fight for Goryeo
For your luck...
your luck in the war
It's not about the cup
Have you poisoned the tea?
I...
I'll drink the poison you poured for me
And one last thing...
Whoever tries to drive a wedge between us with their dirty words, it doesn’t matter
I wish our friendship will forever remain the same.
I am very grateful for your sincerity
Your Majesty, have you seen what kind of heart your brother has?
How can I be away from a brother like him?
Please cancel your order and do not send it to Shinzhu
The water for tea has run out.
I'll go and get more
I'll be gone for a while
Thanks for watching with us!
Release group MANIA
http://doramamania.mybb.ru
http://vk.com/doramamania
Scarlet Hearts: Ryeo
In the room of the court lady Hae Soo
poison and a precious necklace were found
Court Lady Hae Soo
arrested for attempted murder
Why did you arrest an innocent child?
I think you know who's behind this
What kind of person did you risk your life to protect?
I won't let Su suffer
I'll definitely find evidence
Hae Soo
will be executed for attempting to kill the prince
Su!